ACTWU's International Affairs Department Records 5619/032
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Trade Law. Changes [folder 1 of 2], 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Trade Law. Changes [folder 2 of 2], 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Trade Law. Legislation, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Trade Law Reform, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- U.S. Government. Bills (Box 7, Folder 20)
- U.S. Government. Press Releases, 1977- 1980 (Box 7, Folder 21)